(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
Chris Anderson: You guys were amazing.
كريس أندرسون: لقد كنتم مذهلين.
That's amazing.
ذلك مدهش.
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
You just don't hear that every day.
لا يسمع المرء ذلك يوميا.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
Usman, the official story is that
عثمان، الرواية الرسمية هي أنه
you learned to play the guitar
تعلمت عزف الغيتار
by watching Jimmy Page on YouTube.
من خلال مشاهدة صفحة جيمي على يوتيوب.
Usman Riaz: Yes, that was the first one. And then I --
عثمان رياز: نعم، ذلك كان أول واحد. ثم -
That was the first thing I learned,
كان ذلك أول شيء تعلمته،
and then I started progressing to other things.
وبعد ذلك بدأت أتقدم إلى أشياء أخرى.
And I started watching Kaki King a lot,
وبدأت في مشاهدة كاكي كينغ كثيرا،
and she would always cite Preston Reed as a big influence,
ودائما ما تذكر بريستون ريد كمؤثر كبير،
so then I started watching his videos,
وبالتالي بدأت أشاهد فيديوهاته،
and it's very surreal right now to be --
والأمر يفوق الخيال الآن أن أكون --
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
CA: Was that piece just now,
ك. أ: هل كانت تلك القطعة قبل قليل،
that was one of his songs that you learned, or how did that happen?
تلك كانت أحد أغانيك التي تعلمت، أو كيف حصل ذلك؟
UR: I'd never learned it before,
ع. ر: لم أتعلمها من قبل،
but he told me that we would be playing that on stage,
لكنه قال لي أننا سنعزف ذلك على الخشبة،
so I was familiar with it, so that's why I had so much more fun learning it.
وبالتالي كنت مطلعا عليها، ولهذا استمتعت كثيرا بتعلمها.
And it finally happened, so ...
وقد حصلت أخيرا، وبالتالي...
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
CA: Preston, from your point of view,
ك. أ: بريستون، من وجهة نظرك،
I mean, you invented this like 20 years ago, right?
أقصد، كنت اخترعت هذا قبل حوالي 20 سنة مضت، أليس كذلك؟
How does it feel to see someone like this
كيف تشعر حين ترى شخص هكذا
come along taking your art and doing so much with it?
يأتي فيما بعد ويأخذ فنك ويحقق به الكثير؟
Preston Reed: It's mind-blowing,
ريد بريستون: إنه أمر مذهل،
and I feel really proud, really honored.
وأشعر بالفخر والأعتزاز حقاً.
And he's a wonderful musician, so it's cool.
وهو موسيقار رائع، وبالتالي فالأمر رائع.
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
CA: I guess, I don't think there is like a one-minute other piece you guys can do?
ك.أ : أفترض، لا أظن أن هناك قطعة أخرى في دقيقة يمكنكم أن تعزفوها؟
Can you? Do you jam? Do you have anything else?
هل تستطيعون؟ هل تعزفون؟ هل لديكم أي شيء آخر؟
PR: We haven't prepared anything.
ب. ر: لم نقم بإعداد أي شيء.
CA: There isn't. I'll tell you what.
ك. أ: لا يوجد. سوف أقول لكم ماذا.
If you have another 30 or 40 seconds,
إذا كان لديك 30 أو 40 ثانية أخرى،
and you have another 30 or 40 seconds,
ولديكم 30 أو 40 ثانية أخرى،
and we just see that, I just think --
ونحن نرى أنه، أنا أعتقد --
I can feel it. We want to hear a little more.
أستطيع تحسسه. نحن نريد أن نسمع أكثر قليلاً.
And if it goes horribly wrong, no worries.
وإن حدث خطأ فادح، فلا تقلقوا.
(Applause)
(تصفيق)
(Laughter)
(ضحك)
(Music)
(موسيقى)
(Applause)
(تصفيق)